bogglesworldesl.com 2019-01-21

# Presentation: Youngsan

This privacy statement covers the site www.bogglesworldesl.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.   
1.      What personally identifiable information Lanternfish collects.  
2.      What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.  
3.      What organization collects the information.   
4.      How Lanternfish ESL uses the information.  
5.      With whom Lanternfish may share user information.   
6.      What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.   
7.      What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Lanternfish control.   
8.      How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Chris Gunn at [gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com](mailto:gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com). 

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection:  
** Lanternfish uses third party ad servers:

[Burstmedia.com](http://burstmedia.com/),  [Fastclick.com](http://fastclick.com/), Adify, Commission Junction, Allposters.com and [Google Adsense](http://google.com/). Google Adsense in turn allows other advertising agencies to advertise through them and so by extension they advertise on our site too. This includes Doubleclick.Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

These third party ad servers only collect non-personally identifiable information such as I.P. addresses and collect aggregate statistics such as page views. For more details about the information that they collect please view their privacy statements.

Lanternfish ESL collects both aggregate information throughout the site and personally indentifiable information at one point in the site, the discussion forums.

Registration  
No information is required to register for this site. However, registration may be required to use some sections of the member forum. See profile below:

Information Use  
Except for the discussion forums, any information collected on this site by Lanternfish ESL is of a non-personal nature.  Boggle'sWorld does not store or keep personal information on record but does keep aggregate numbers on the number of visitors, method of arriving at bogglesworldesl.com, location by region, servers, monitor type and operating systems. __T__ _ _o use some sections of the discussion forum, however, users may be required to provide some personal information as listed in the profile below__. The information collected in registration will not be used for any purposes other than administering the board and will never be given or sold to third parties under any circumstance. However, there is always a security risk from criminal parties hacking into the MY SQL database that we use. 

Profile  
Lanternfish ESL does collect profiles of users who wish to register for the discussion forum. The discussion forum is made from PHPBB2 software. The only information that registrants must supply is a valid email address. However, the registration sheet does allow them to provide more information such as job, country, interests, and other electonic communication channels that they use.  For more information on the type of information that can be supplied visit the [registration page](https://bogglesworldesl.com/phpbb/phpBB2/profile.php?mode=register&sid=0b5744240a88fddd5e1e0ee58314b2e6).

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  We use both session ID cookies and persistent ID cookies.  For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.   
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.  

**Third Party Advertising**

THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT! Third party advertising partners sometimes conduct surveys or place ads that lead to pages that collect information.  Any personally identifiable information that they collect will actually be collected off site (i.e. at another website) but since the ads originated from our site, it may appear that we are collecting information.  

These third party advertisers include Google Adsense and the Hotchalk advertising network.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files.  This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Communications from the Site**

Newsletter  
Currently, we do not have a newsletter btu if we do this is the policy we will use: If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.  Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Service Announcements  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email.  Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account.  However, these communications are not promotional in nature.  [Users may opt-out of these communications. Please see our Choice and Opt-out section.] 

Customer Service  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

Sharing  
Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

These are the instances in which we will share users??personal information:  
We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties 

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Lanternfish ESL, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Security  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users??information.  When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. Currently, we collect no information such as personnel ID or credit cards.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com <mailto:gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com>

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  

If, however, we are going to use users??personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.  However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.  In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.  

Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Email gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com [gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com](mailto:gunnchris@bogglesworldesl.com)
